<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="22000" point="clan1_sudoport" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-06-17" status="final" >
	<part>
		<line id="1000" speaker="game">Zone 1 Act 1</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="game">Sudo Port</line>
		<narration>The darkness shifts shape into a warm, colorful port town. Rushing into mind are moments, entities, time and space &#x2014; a world. Sun, light, voices. People. Life? Yuki &#x2014; NoLifeQueen &#x2014; gazes about. <comment>Camera dolly out extremely far. Vision text appears for every object in view.</comment>She so expertly imagines the full possibilities and consequences of&#x2014;</narration>
		<line id="3000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">NoLifeQueen, new admin!</line>
		<narration>Hanging from a propellerless helicopter just above the rooftops is a man in pajamas. From the studio-quality driver of a netbook microphone, to his fellow player he communicates:</narration>
		<line id="4000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Get up here.</line>
		<line id="4100" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Try a ladder, Try a rooftop, Try the stairs, try something!</line>
		<narration>For her first trick,</narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen climbs up a ladder and takes too long. The helicopter shoots the ladder down.</narration>
				<line id="5000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Climb faster!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen enters a building and spends too much time in it. The helicopter blows up the insides, launching NoLifeQueen out of a window.</narration>
				<line id="5100" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Move faster!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="3">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen walks up a flight of stairs like she has all the time in the world. The helicopter shoots at her.</narration>
				<line id="5200" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Run faster!</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen finally gets close to the helicopter.</narration>
		<line id="5000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Grab on!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen grabs onto the copter bottom. She and the ally hang for a time. The helicopter repeats its path. Buildigns are long afar. The pair retain their hang to chat.<comment>The music stops.</comment></narration>
		<line id="6000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">So this is shooting game?</line>
		<line id="7000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">For the next six months.</line>
		<narration>The helicopter rises. The two continue chatting. The wind a-whistles.</narration>
		<line id="8000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Listen:</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">We've got a lot of customers still paying twice a month for this game.</line>
		<line id="10000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">We better keep it playable. That means taking out this griefer.</line>
		<line id="11000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Do you know how to form a Clan?</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="12000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">I'll figure it out myself.</line>
				<line id="13000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Good luck, then.</line>
				<narration>Silence. The wind whistles. The man stares at NoLifeQueen.<comment>The Player is expected to act.</comment></narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="13000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">I don't know how.</line>
				<narration>The man pushes her off the copter.<comment>Unavoidable.</comment></narration>
				<line id="14000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Time to find out!</line>
			</choice>

		<line id="12000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">Take the copter down!</line>
		<narration>How do you take down a helicopter?<comment>Quite a few possibilities here. Player can hijack the copter and pilot it down, player can get a few bros in a Clan and weigh the copter down, player can defeat copter pilots and jump off.</comment></narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen jacks the copter.<comment>Impressment mode begins when the helicopter gets close to the ground. Impressment is inversely proportional to the speed of the helicopter landing.</comment></narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen drops.<comment>Impressment mode begins as NoLifeQueen falls. Impressment depends on how well she lands on her feet.</comment>The helicopter raises to the level of the buildings</narration>
				<line id="13000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">We have a flying machine to sink.</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="3">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen gets the pilot out of the cockpit and roughs him up. Both of the two fall out of the copter together.<comment>Impressment depends on smoothness of foot-landing in comparison to the pilot. If the Player gets hit by the copter, dead.</comment></narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>The team cheers. They just took down a helicopter! Good little Yuki did it in a sun-dress, no less. She cheers, holding down her hat and the enemy is afoot.</narration>
		<line id="14000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">The pilots are escaping.</line>
		<narration>The man motions NoLifeQueen's clan over. He laughs.</narration>
		<line id="15000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">We have cheaters to catch.</line>
		<narration>After the two pilots Yuki's clan marathon-sprints. They shove bystanders aside, stomp plants and kick poles.<comment>Characters are slowed down when they bump into others while running.</comment> No player pants. From realized anaerobic calm rises another chat.</narration>
		<line id="16000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">So you're from Sega?</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="man" voicelang="en">North American branch. Real Name's Davis.</line>
		<narration>So is his screen name.</narration>
		<line id="18000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">And these are my bros from San Fran.</line>
		<narration>They wave hello and bathe Yuki in compliments.</narration>
		<line id="19000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Together, we form INTERPOL.</line>
		<line id="20000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">INTERPOL?</line>
		<line id="21000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">The Internet Police!</line>
		<narration>Davis and NoLifeQueen hear a voice in the distance. The target is on a soapbox, yelling his thoughts to malleable ears.<comment>At any point, the player can knock the guy off.</comment></narration>
		<line id="22000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">Video games are for children!</line>
		<line id="23000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">These mass marketed murder simulators mutilate their minds!</line>
		<narration>Davis throws NoLifeQueen a rocket launcher.<comment>This weapon is easiest for causing a ruckus. The Player must be careful not to hit the crowd. Customer Loss Condition: a gun object is destroyed.</comment></narration>
		<line id="24000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">Every dead policeman is another Virginia Tech.</line>
		<line id="25000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">Every slain monster is Akihabara twice!</line>
		<line id="26000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">I will delete every projectile weapon!</line>
		<line id="27000" speaker="target" voicelang="en">Such is the decree of the Fathers Against Guns.</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen hits The Father.</narration>
				<line id="28000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">Argh! Violence!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen accidentally hits the crowd.</narration>
				<line id="29000" speaker="crowd" voicelang="lt">The admins are hurting innocent players!</line>
				<line id="30000" speaker="crowd" voicelang="ja">Maybe the protester is right.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>The Target and his Clan of supporters begin to delete weapons. If a weapon exists, it is deleted. If someone is holding it, it is stolen.</narration>
		<line id="31000" speaker="game">Don't let them delete weapons!</line>
		<narration>After a while, all the Father and his sons flee.</narration>
		<line id="32000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">They're taking the rest of the guns to a warehouse?</line>
		<line id="33000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Only a gun controls a gun.</line>
		<line id="34000" speaker="davis" voicelang="fr">Let's get to the warehouse.</line>
		<narration>The sounds of families, matters, and better-to-do things are heard through the microphones of NoLifeQueen's Clan. They overpower the noise of the mere video game. Allies begin to log out. NoLifeQueen double, triple, and quadruple takes.</narration>
		<line id="34100" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Hey, where are you all going?</line>
		<line id="35000" speaker="player" voicelang="en">Wife and kids are home from soccer practice.</line>
		<line id="36000" speaker="player" voicelang="en">Gotta get ready for the night shift.</line>
		<line id="37000" speaker="player" voicelang="en">I'm going to water my petunias.</line>
		<narration>Just outside the warehouse, at the dock. Crates are scattered about. It's quiet. It's dark. It's cold. NoLifeQueen shivers. She looks around. <comment>NoLifeQueen looks at the camera and motions the player over. She whispers.</comment></narration>
		<line id="35000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">This is strange. I actually feel cold in real life&#x2014;</line>
		<narration>Behind the crates revealed are The Father's men! They lunge at NoLifeQueen. Davis yells.</narration>
		<line id="36000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Stop, don't shoot!</line>
		<narration>Punched is Davis, in the face. There is but one projectile weapon in view.</narration>
		<line id="37000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Yuki, get into the warehouse. We'll take care of these jokers.</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen runs inside.</narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen stays and fights alongside Davis and his bros.<comment>The player now may take the earlier mentioned projectile weapon warehouse.</comment>She and davis infiltrate the warehouse, its doors closing before any other after.</narration>

		<narration>The Warehouse. It's pitch black. A spotlight shines on NoLifeQueen. Someone rushes by. A voice is heard from a dark corner.</narration>
		<line id="38000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">You, too, are with the Sega Corporation, I suppose?</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen yells into the darkness.</narration>
		<line id="39000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">I'm not just with them. I am them.</line>
		<line id="40000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Yuki Soleil-Takeshi, Vice President of Sega.</line>
		<line id="41000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">More like Vice President of Death.</line>
		<narration>Yuki laughs.</narration>
		<line id="42000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">Silence!</line>
		<narration>The Father fires the first shot. The game is afoot.<comment>The spotlight in the room swerves around. The room is littered with pistols. The spotlight shifts around the room, and The Father makes an effort to push every weapon and himself into the dark. He bursts from the darkness to occasionally melee attack.</comment>NoLifeQueen defeats The Father. The father kneels on the ground.</narration>
		<line id="43000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Go to your bookshelf and look at this game's box.</line>
		<narration>For a time, The Father's avatar does not move. Away from keyboard. <comment>The player can walk around safely at this time.</comment>He comes back.</narration>
		<line id="44000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">What is the rating on that box?</line>
		<narration>The Father gulps.</narration>
		<line id="45000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">M, for Mature.</line>
		<line id="46000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Just like cigarettes, alcohol, and pornography.</line>
		<line id="47000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">While you sit and protest the inevitable,</line>
		<line id="48000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">your child could be getting plastered.</line>
		<line id="49000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">And how am I to stop the world from harming my child?</line>
		<line id="50000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Be a better parent.</line>
		<narration>The father sulks. He has one hit-point left.</narration>
		<line id="51000" speaker="father" voicelang="en">Terminate my account.</comment>
		<narration>Yuki doesn't know how to terminate accounts. She fiddles around with the controls.<comment>This is done peacefully. All of the buttons randomly flicker between "Terminate" and other random nonviolent actions.</comment> Yuki deletes The Father's account. His avatar explodes into a flurry of hex and caught exceptions.</narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen ditched Davis to defeat the boss. Davis died in the heat of the battle. The Father's grunts, directionless and angry, enter the warehouse to find NoLifeQueen.</narration>
				<line id="52000" speaker="grunt" voicelang="en">Get her!</line>
				<narration>The grunts defeat NoLifeQueen. Game Over.</narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>The Father's laughs can be heard through the stream of old, corrupted data. The warehouse explodes with Davis and NoLifeQueen in it. Game Over.</narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
	</part>
</scriptment>