<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="34000" point="clan3_fortressbeach" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-07-15" status="final">
	<part>
		<narration><comment>The music of Suntory Hall echoes into silence.</comment>NoLifeQueen and Yuki are one. They share the same face. They share the same pain. Some brilliant process of a digital image caught all the girl's emotion. Is the computer smart, or the lady vain&#x2014;</narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Wake up!</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Huh?</line>
		<line id="3000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Some new player managed to find this cycle's root directory.</line>
		<line id="4000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">The corrupt data and rogue glitch before you is the result</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">of brute-forcing the root password with an army of cheap rigs with bad RAM.</line>
		<line id="6000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="en">I'd teach the thrifty cracker a lesson, but I don't want to break my computer.</line>
		<narration>The water stands still, while the sand ripples. Droplets of ocean float from ground to air. Clouds drop from the sky. Player characters, unable to assist the Internet Police, walk on their hairs and think on their toes.<comment>A dialogue box flashes for a split second.</comment></narration>
		<line id="7000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Not it!</line>
		<line id="8000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="en">Not it!</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Shoot.</line>
		<line id="10000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">There are no Clans here. We'll cover you, Yukes!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen and company make their way across the shards of broken data. Guns are shooting guns. Humans are walking upside down. Random objects are disappearing. Someone picks up a gun and it turns into a player from another zone.</narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen makes it into the castle at the end of the beach. Yuki sighs.</narration>
		<line id="11000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Why did dad have to design the game like this?</line>
		<narration>A strong, courageous, talent-fostering man appears from behind a pillar. He is dressed in a jogging-suit. He runs around the castle, commanding a multitude of corrupt adding-machines.</narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">Because he appointed a prince.</line>
		<line id="13000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">Yuki, if we destroy the current configuration files, the game will recycle.</line>
		<line id="14000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">This world can be shaped to our desires.</line>
		<line id="15000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">You know nothing of this world, JJ.</line>
		<line id="16000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Dad wouldn't want men who desire control to ruin The Clan's chaos.</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">Is the desire for discord not a form of concord?</line>
		<line id="18000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">Dad saw me in the hall.</line>
		<line id="19000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="ja">He told me, "I expected Yuki."</line>
		<line id="20000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Well, when I saw you, I expected you.</line>
		<line id="21000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Live your life, not your father's.</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Now get the hell out of my game.</line>
		<narration>NoLifeKing slaps NoLifeQueen.</narration>
		<line id="23000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">No.</line>
		<line id="24000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">What the hell, you just slapped your sister!</line>
		<line id="25000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">In a video game!</line>
		<line id="26000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Don't you get it? It doesn't matter! Video games don't matter!</line>
		<line id="27000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">I'd shoot you if it meant I'd win!</line>
		<line id="28000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">What of the intent?</line>
		<line id="29000" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">I'll show you intent!</line>
		<line id="29100" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">We've disappointed our own parents, Yuki &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="29200" speaker="nolifeking" voicelang="fr">We've disappointed the ones who gave us the privilege of living!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeKing knocks a pillar over. The moment it hits the ground, it transforms into a helicopter. <comment>Because the fortress is corrupt, this presents a multitude of unforseen opportunities to the opponent... and the Player. The pillars turn into vehicles when someone hits them. The vehicles explode seconds after boarding them. The ground type changes when something explodes on them. Water causes things to bounce. Solid ground submerges things. You know the drill, freak the Player out.</comment>The game is afoot.</narration>
		<narration>NoLifeKing is taking quite the beating. His hit-point counter nears zero. Yuki gloats.</narration>
		<line id="30000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Is blindly following a distorted vision of your inheritance called "living?"</line>
		<narration>Just before defeat, NoLifeKing presses a button. A laser beam defeats NoLifeQueen. Game Over. JJ sniffles. NoLifeKing rises.</narration>
		<line id="31000" speaker="jj" voicelang="fr">It's called succession.</line>
	</part>
</narration>