<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->






<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="1000" point="beginning" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="1986-09-17" status="final">
	<part name="train" fictionaldate="1986-09-17">
	<!-- The fictionaldate was put here to demonstrate the use of part-level fictionaldates. -->

			<narration lineid="">1986. On the cold, hard floor of a French connector lie Asami and Jacques, bedsheets askew. The lady breathes hard; the gentleman breathes smoke. Asami fidgets.</narration>
			<line id="3000" voicelang="fr" speaker="asami">The clocks are frowning at me.</line>
			<narration>Jacques yawns. Jacques rises. Asami yells! She seizes the sheets and covers her mate's shame. Also covering herself, she lingers but a stumble away.<comment>The controls appear for the first time. This is the Player's first interaction with the game. This must happen less than ten seconds after startup. Jacques is the Leading Character. The Player can walk around the train as Jacques. Asami follows extremely close, covering the man's body with a towel.</comment>There are few clocks. Calendars litter the train's walls.<comment>When the player nears Jacques to a calendar, the camera begins to zoom in on the calendar.</comment></narration>
			<line id="4000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">Clocks shall not frown on the boldest of mates. Great spawn are born in spontaneity.</line>
			<line id="5000" voicelang="fr" speaker="asami">Is it mere "spontaneity" at such an hour?</line>
			<line id="4000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">Think not of an hour, but of the year.</line>
			<line id="5000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">I am in need of succession.</line>
			<line id="6000" voicelang="fr" speaker="asami">Typical father, exerting his unfulfilled desires on unborn children.</line>
			<narration>Bracing the shake of the cab, Jacques stares down the sky.</narration>
			<line id="7000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">Unfulfilled? Nonsense. Someone must take my place on the throne.</line>
			<line id="8000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">That someone will be my son.</line>
			<line id="9000" voicelang="fr" speaker="jacques">My talented, brilliant visionary of a son.</line>
			<comment>By the time Jacques says this, the camera will have completely zoomed in on a calendar. A song begins to play. The environment makes an abrupt change in synchronization to each note in the lead guitar riff. The calendar changes. The date changes. The wallpaper changes. The day-light changes.</comment>
			</part>
</scriptment>