<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="9000" point="cannes_end" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="1997-01-13" status="final" >
	<part name="first_day">
		<narration>Yuki looks around. Signs are in Japanese. Voices are in Japanese. People are in Japanese. JJ has a front seat. The teacher raises her hand.</narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Class, welcome our new student, Yuki&#x2014;</line>
		<narration>The teacher pauses and glances at Yuki. She looks back at the paper. She again looks at Yuki—</narration>
		<line id="2000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Takeshi.</line>
		<line id="3000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Alright, take a seat.</line>
		<narration><comment>The Player walks Yuki to the back of the classroom. Every seat looks suspicious upon nearing it.</comment>To which seat does Yuki belong? There are ten in the back of the classroom, all of them not exclusively for Burakumin or Brazilians, but for that united-yet-fallen sort of lost children. Foreigners. Newcomers. Those unfamiliar with the village, malleable, longing for proper assimilation at the hands of anyone who dare provide it. Yuki sits. Two children heckle her.</narration>
		<line id="4000" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">So what part of Japan are you from?</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">France.</line>
		<line id="6000" speaker="child_2" voicelang="ja">And here I thought all blondes came from America.</line>
		<line id="6100" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">I hear our cartoons are pretty popular in France.</line>
		<line id="6200" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Good for the cartoons.</line>
		<line id="7000" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">Did you remember to do the homework?</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="8000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">What homework?</line>
				<line id="9000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Everyone, take out Friday's homework!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="10000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Yes!</line>
				<line id="11000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Everyone, take out Friday's homework!</line>
				<line id="11100" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">For today, you were supposed to draw a picture and tell the class about someone that inspires you.</line>
				<line id="12000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Since even our foreign student had a weekend's advance, I expect you all did the assignment.</line>
				<line id="13000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">After all, your entire participation grade depends on it.</line>
				<line id="14000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Oh god.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<line id="15000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">So we may have a proper introduction to them, we'll have our new students present first.</line>
		<line id="15100" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Jacques!</line>
		<narration>The class claps for the new student.</narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="16000" speaker="game">Clap for him.</line>
				<narration>Yuki claps.</narration>
				<line id="17000" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">Yeah! Even the foreigner approves!</line>
				<line id="18000" speaker="child_2" voicelang="ja">Doesn't that make it uncool?</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="19000" speaker="game">Screw that.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<line id="20000" speaker="jj" voicelang="ja">Calm down, everyone. I haven't even gotten to the good part yet!</line>
		<narration>Yuki gasps. JJ takes out a crayon drawing of Asami.</narration>
		<line id="21000" speaker="jj" voicelang="ja">This is my mom.</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="jj" voicelang="ja">She's a musician.</line>
		<line id="23000" speaker="jj" voicelang="ja">She played a really important show at harughlegargle blahblah sphinxterstankle.</line>
		<narration>Yuki springs up and flings the desk astray.</narration>
		<line id="24000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">What! When did you learn Japanese?</line>
		<narration>Everyone hushes Yuki.<comment>If the Player doesn't make Yuki sit, someone else will.</comment>The teacher sits back and waves her hand.</narration>
		<line id="24100" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Jacques, continue.</line>
		<line id="25000" speaker="jj" voicelang="ja">She inspires me because hurkadurka derpaderp hurr durr genuflectacatamaran.</line>
		<narration>With each phrase of the tongue, Yuki's heart beats faster. She clasps her temples. She needs to get away from this. She needs to leave. She needs an excuse! The teacher continues.</narration>
		<line id="26000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">You mean, your mom is Dr. Takeshi, ljfoijoiejoaijwofiajwogijawoiegj?</line>

		<line id="27000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="ja">mahagbomanring hopralofeeblenfro.</line>
		<narration>Yuki raises her hand. She sweats, shakes, eyes fixed on the exit. The teacher points at her.</narration>
		<line id="28000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Oh shizzle ameliabedelia dynamite?</line>

		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="29000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">I need to go to the bathroom!</line>
				<narration>Yuki dashes and hits the teacher on the way to the door closest to the bathroom.</narration>
				
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="30000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">I need to get a drink!</line>
				<narration>Yuki dashes and trips over a desk on the way to the door closest to the water fountain.</narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration><comment>A self-conscious moment. Until she goes back to class, the camera remains extremely close to Yuki and out of the player's control. Action buttons shuffle around. The Main Action changes to rocking back and forth.</comment>Wherever she is, Yuki drops into fetal position. She begins to whisper to herself.</narration>
		<line id="31000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">In the womb, there were no languages.</line>
		<line id="32000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">I'm stupid.</line>
		<narration>Yuki whispers more frantically.</narration>
		<line id="33000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Japanese language characters cover a larger range of the Unicode character space.</line>
		<line id="34000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">The language is more complex. Only smart people can speak it.</line>
		
		<line id="35000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">JJ can speak it. The kids can speak it. I can't.</line>
		<narration>The Administrator sees Yuki. He grimaces, grabs her by the arm, and drags her towards the classroom. Yuki is compliant. She can hear the sound of cheering from outside.</narration>
		<line id="36000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Japanese people are smarter than me. </line>
		<line id="37000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Japanese people don't need dye to be black and beautiful.</line>
		<line id="37100" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">"Influence is the marriage of intelligence and appearance."</line>
		<narration>Yuki slows down.</narration>
		<line id="38000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Japanese people are better than me.</line>
		<narration>The Administrator throws Yuki back into the classroom. She trips and falls. Except JJ, everyone laughs. The Administrator silences them.</narration>
		<line id="39000" speaker="administrator" voicelang="ja">Damn misfit kid. Found her skipping class.</line>
		<narration>The Administrator points at Yuki.</narration>
		<line id="39100" speaker="administrator" voicelang="ja">You're making your brother look bad.</line>
		<narration>The Administrator exits. As if nothing happened, the teacher continues.</narration>
		<line id="40000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Yuki, your turn to present.</line>
		<narration>It's cold outside. The windows are open. Someone should close them. Hopefully, the coffee is still warm. The teacher sits down and has a cup. Did anyone watch last week's episode of Pokémon? Everyone chats amongst each other. Yuki looks down.</narration>
		<line id="41000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Present, huh?</line>
		<narration>The teacher waves her hand while taking a sip.</narration>
		<line id="42000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Present the homework.</line>
		
		<line id="43000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Homework, huh?</line>
		<line id="44000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">You did read the paper I gave you, right?</line>
		<narration>The teacher puts a piece of paper on the desk. Yuki picks it up and has a look.<comment>The player is urged to pick it up and take a look. Yuki urges the player to zoom in. The letters on the paper shift around. Constant failing Vision texts appear. </comment>The kid has a lot of symbols to learn.</narration>
		<line id="45000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">I can't read.</line>
		<narration>The teacher face-palms. The students guffaw.</narration>
		<line id="46000" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">What kind of fifth grader can't read?</line>
		<narration>The teacher silences the class.</narration>
		<line id="47000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Yuki, draw the person who inspires you on that chalkboard.</line>
		<narration>The teacher points at the board and throws Yuki a piece of chalk. <comment>The player has to pick it up and go to the chalkboard to continue drawing.</comment> She begins to draw. The chalk runs out. The teacher throws her another piece. It runs out. Students begin to take pieces of chalk from nooks and crannies of the room and toss it at Yuki. <comment>The chalk is thrown in random places. Some pieces bounce off of Yuki. The Player is to retrieve them and return to the board.</comment>Yuki keeps drawing. She keeps running out. She draws. She runs out. She draws. She runs out. She sighs. Covered in chalk, Yuki stands tall and presents her source of inspiration:</narration>
		<line id="48000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Sonic the Hedgehog.</line>
		<narration>The teacher facepalms. The students guffaw.</narration>
		<line id="49000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">I said "person." Like family, or friends, or... </line>
		<line id="50000" speaker="child_1" voicelang="ja">He's not even on playstation!</line>
		<line id="51000" speaker="child_2" voicelang="ja">Or any good games.</line>
		<line id="52000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">I can't let an illiterate child tarnish my reputation...</line>
		<line id="53000" speaker="tokyo_teacher" voicelang="ja">Better dump her on the remedial teachers.</line>
		<line id="54000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">This is not my classroom.</line>
		<narration>Yuki gave up. Years passed. Every year, her hair was further in disarray. Every year, her work became sloppier. Every year, she broke down at least once in every classroom. She barely passed her remedial classes. She barely passed anything.<comment>The Player can walk around. There are constant sudden-cuts from classroom to classroom, a year between each. In each cut, Yuki holds a failed paper. In each cut, Yuki looks worse off.</comment></narration>
		</part>
</scriptment>