<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="18000" point="yuki_bar" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-06-11" status="final" >
	<part>
		<narration>Friday evening, after work. Yuki makes plans. </narration>
		<line id="900" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Well, guys&#x2014;</line>
		<narration><comment>A split second after the Player chooses a hobby event, Nozomi cancels her decision.</comment>Nozomi jumps up.</narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Great week, everyone! Let's go to the bar!</line>
		<narration>Yuki shivers and twitches.</narration>
		<line id="2000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Yes sure she is has good idea we will drinking is good for your health and your mind!</line>
		<narration>.<comment>Sudden cut from the studio to the bar.</comment>The entrance of the bar. The whole team shuffles past Yuki, into the bar. Yuki looks at the entrance. Something is suspicious about this door. Yuki marches on. She stops just before the door. A dialogue box pops up.</narration>
		<line id="3000" speaker="game">Would you like to enter the bar?</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="4000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Yes</line>
				<narration>Yuki hears a harsh beeping sound. Invalid action.</narration>
				<line id="5000" speaker="game">Would you like to enter the bar?</line>
				<narration>Yuki cannot enter.<comment>Continue to ask the player until they say No.</comment></narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="6000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">No</line>
				<line id="7000" speaker="game">Good looks, Madeline. Run along, now.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>A college-age girl with black-dyed hair emerges from the other side of the fortress. She's dressed to a drunk old pervert's strangest fantasies.</narration>
		<line id="8000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">My deepest apologies, Mademoiselle. This hostess club is Japanese Only.</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Japanese Only?</line>
		<line id="10000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">Japanese Only.</line>
		<narration>The sun begins to set. The Tokyo summer heat subsides. Yuki takes a long hard look at this girl.</narration>
		<line id="11000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">You're not Japanese.</line>
		<narration>The hostess folds her arms.<comment>Dialogue boxes for response appear the instant the hostess begins to talk.</comment></narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">Look, blondie. I got tuition to pay and you're wasting my time&#x2014;</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="13000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">How dare you shield yourself behind the nature of your work.</line>
				<line id="14000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">How dare you toss around "Mademoiselle" when you know exactly what it implies&#x2014;</line>
				<narration>The hostess flails her arms.</narration>
				<line id="15000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">It implies that for politeness' sake,</line>
				<line id="16000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">I choose to ignore the crow's feet under your makeup!</line>
				<narration>Yuki sniffles.</narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="17000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Those aren't your clothes.</line>
				<line id="18000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">That's not your hair.</line>
				<line id="18100" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">These aren't your words.</line>
				<line id="19000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">This is my job.</line>
				<line id="20000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">I don't know where you came from where you didn't have to get by,</line>
				<line id="21000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">But we're in a recession! People need money! No exceptions!</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>Silence. Yuki glares at this girl.</narration>

		<line id="13000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">What's your name?</line>
		<line id="14000" speaker="hostess" voicelang="fr">Ayane.</line>
		<line id="15000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Ayane what?</line>
		<line id="16000" speaker="ayane" voicelang="fr">Ayane, dammit.</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="ayane" voicelang="fr">Now beat it, blondie, before I get the muscles.</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>Yuki stands until Ayane gets the muscles.</narration>
				<line id="18000" speaker="ayane" voicelang="ja">Hey, Suji! Une fille blanc.</line>
				<line id="19000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Oh god.</line>
				<narration>A voice rumbles from the door.</narration>
				<line id="20000" speaker="suji" voicelang="fr">I love seeing what white girls do in the face of prejudice!</line>

				<narration>Suji bursts out of the front door and charges at Yuki.</narration>
					<condition>
						<choice number="1">
							<comment>The player runs away.</comment>
							<narration>Yuki runs, screaming. Yards away, she catches her breath.</narration>
							<line id="21000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I ran?</line>
							<comment>Yuki looks at the camera.</comment>
							<line id="21100" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">Wow, I'm lame.</line>
						</choice>
						<choice number="2">
							<comment>The Player stands Yuki there.</comment>
							<narration>Yuki stands tall still. Suji stops straight in front of her. He shields his face.</narration>
							<line id="22000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suji">Oh.</line>
							<narration>He takes hold of Yuki by the shoulders, turns her around, and escorts her off the premises. <comment>The Player can still move Yuki in the opposite direction, but the man is well synchronized to Yuki's axis. He keeps pushing. Escort is inevitable.</comment>Far from the bar, Yuki stumbles, then bursts into laughter.</narration>
						</choice>
				</condition>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>Yuki walks away.</narration>
				<line id="23000" voicelang="fr" speaker="ayane">Good night, Madame.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<comment>After walking away, the camera is positioned so that the player is unable to see the bar.</comment>
		<line id="24000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I better get home.</line>
		<narration>Yuki begins to walk home. Before Yuki's Ears is heavenly music in the distance. When she reaches her house, the music fades away.<comment>Any action the player does that involves going through a door will lead to a sudden cut to the train. For example...</comment>Yuki turns the knob of her front door.<comment>Sudden cut so that Yuki, in the same position, is moving through the turnstile of the train station. Small delay.</comment></narration>
		<narration>Yuki is on a train. Next to Yuki, holding hands are two Salarymen. One French, one Japanese. The Japanese man stares into the Frenchman's eyes and nudges him with his nose. Passing to a seat on the train is a hot chick. The French breaks away to get a good look. The Japanese slap him. Yuki pays them no mind.</narration>
		<line id="25000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">It's Saturday night and I'm not a complete loser anymore, right?</line>
		<narration>On Yuki's other side, playing the plumber-who-races-dinosaurs game are two children, one French, one Japanese. The French child stares at her screen in disbelief. She's in last place. The French turns off the game-system. The Japanese pout. Yuki pays them no mind.</narration>
		<line id="26000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I shouldn't be at home when people with friends are out and about.</line>
		<narration>Yuki stands up and holds the bar. This is her stop.<comment>Sudden cut to front door of the arcade.</comment>Club Sega, Akihabara. The outside of the club looks a bit run down. Maintenance is expensive. We're in a recession. The inside of the club is completely different. Swing music blares. All are in dress and suit. A man at the front looks at Yuki. He dashes into the building and returns with a different man to greet her.</narration>
		<line id="27000" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">Evening, Mademoiselle, and welcome to Club Sega.</line>
		<narration>The man begins to follow Yuki throughout the arcade, watching her closely.<comment>The Player can continue walking into the arcade; the greeter follows Yuki, burdening her, becoming part of the party.</comment></narration>
		<line id="28000" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">Please do not hack our computerized credit system or our power grid.</line>
		<line id="28100" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">You are a hacker, right?</line>
		<narration>Yuki gets ready to answer&#x2014;<comment>Dialogue box pops up for a split second and disappears, all options blank.</comment></narration>
		<line id="28200" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I, uh&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="29000" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">Please do not physically harm opponent players in the event that you are about to lose.</line>
		<line id="30000" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">If you cannot read the health warnings on the arcade games, please do not play them&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="30100" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">Currently, the second, third, and fourth floors are unavailable.</line>
		<line id="31000" voicelang="fr" speaker="man">All arcade machines have been reinforced with titanium for your banging pleasure.</line>
		<narration>Yuki pushes him away.</narration>
		<line id="32000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">Yeah, alright.</line>
		<narration>The man walks away, still watching Yuki.<comment>He is not dismissed from the party.</comment></narration>
		<narration>This amusement parlor is different. There are no UFO catchers here. There are no horse-machines here. There are no photo booths or pachinko boxes. Only worlds and their masters. Only culture and its curators. The patrons of the parlor put passion into their play. Cigar smoke fills the air. Scotch glasses lie on control panels. People bang machines. People yell. People cheer. People are real. This is beyond an arcade; this is a club.</narration>
		<line id="33000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I knew people around here actually cared about games, but this is nuts.</line>
		<line id="34000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I better get my credits and see what the fuss is all about.</line>
		<narration>Yuki goes to the credits machine. She takes out her money.</narration>
		<line id="35000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">This is only enough Yen for one game.</line>
		<line id="36000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">I just rode all the way here, and all I get is one game?</line>
		<narration>Yuki clenches her card and laughs.<comment>Camera dolly out on Yuki. Show the player the variety of arcade games available for play. Allow player to choose one. </comment></narration>
		<line id="37000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">And so, economics forces upon a westerner the One-Credit Clear.</line>
		<line id="38000" voicelang="en" speaker="yuki">Play on.</line>
		<narration>Yuki plays a game. Two men pass by, one looks as if he is an ally. "Suzuki," says his nametag.</narration>
		<line id="39000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">...arcade gaming is the supernova of this recession.</line>
		<line id="40000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">The hardcore may adore the new, game-heavy, high-quality setup,</line>
		<line id="41000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">but we only maintain it because the hardcore are the only ones who still come.</line>
		<line id="42000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">So arcades will become heavens &#x2014; For a few months.</line>
		<line id="43000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">And if this industry doesn't change its models, even Japanese arcades will die.</line>
		<line id="43100" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">I don't think I'll come back if the arcade dies&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="44000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">Takeshi?</line>
		<narration>Yuki continues to play the game as she talks.</narration>
		<line id="45000" voicelang="fr" speaker="yuki">Huh?</line>
		<line id="46000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">So you're the new Vice Prez!</line>
		<line id="47000" voicelang="ja" speaker="yuki">Yeah!</line>
		<line id="48000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">Yu Suzuki. I'm manning Sega's last arcade, so I can't really be at the office.</line>
		<line id="49000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">Anyway, congratulations&#x2014; at the current Sega, Vice Presidents are kings.</line>
		<line id="50000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">I really should find a better way to help from here.</line>
		<line id="51000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">Hey, how about I get you guys computer parts? Somebody's gotta do it.</line>
		<line id="52000" voicelang="ja" speaker="yuki">That's fantastic! We're expanding. You can be in charge of providing us with workstations.</line>
		<line id="53000" voicelang="ja" speaker="suzuki">Yeah, just think&#x2014; Yu Suzuki, Sega's sole connection to cutting-edge technology...</line>
		<comment>The "Concierge" menu appears.</comment>
	</part>
</scriptment>