<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="58000" point="clan6_mtmalcolm" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-08-26" status="final">
	<part>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen and satchmo_omega walk through the greenhouse on the waterfall's slope. The rapids slink over the glass.</narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">This is pretty relaxing.</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">Monsieur Soleil built it as a place for administrators to relax.</line>
		<line id="3000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">But we aren't here to relax, are we?</line>
		<line id="4000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">We're here to delete and sort some files.</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">What kind of files?</line>
		<line id="6000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">The source.</line>
		<line id="7000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">There are gigabytes of unused resources from Phantasy Star 5 here.</line>
		<line id="8000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">If we leave them laying around, we'll have a lot more crackers to deal with.</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Just take the books from the light blue shelves and delete them.</line>
		<narration>Satchmo walks to the other end of the building. Before NoLifeQueen is a row of shelves. <comment>NoLifeQueen urges player to close in on shelf to accurately pick out books. Main action is delete.</comment>NoLifeQueen takes a book. She deletes it. Pages flutter through the calm indoor air, dissipating into clouds of hex.</narration>
		<line id="10000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Meaningless patterns of flashing lights.</line>
		<line id="11000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">We sit in dark rooms laughing and crying for shifting pixels timed to symboled buttons.</line>
		<line id="11100" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">This is how we communicate with computers.</line>
		<narration>Yuki sighs.</narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">My love for the machine stems from its objective linguistics.</line>
		<line id="12100" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Father made computers communicate with us through a simulation.</line>
		<line id="13000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">What did he use?</line>
		<line id="14000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">An abstract, ludologically metaphorical representation of system entities.</line>
		<line id="15000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">A realistic, simulative representation of user actions.</line>
		<line id="16000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">A concrete, narrative exposition of system events.</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Such implementation is still in its infancy, awaiting the harshest of malicious attacks&#x2014;</line>
		<narration>Crashes through the window bring helicopters and army-men and a man in a suit who comes by and greets NoLifeQueen in the face and those army-men push NoLifeQueen and satchmo to the ground and the man who had greeted NoLifeQueen in the face comes down and he says:</narration>
		<line id="18000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">Greetings, minions of the New Parisian-Nagoyan Network!</line>
		<line id="19000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">After much ado about a lot, we proudly present:</line>
		<line id="20000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">The Group's Third Demonstration!</line>
		<line id="21000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">Since our day-longs don't seem to move you, we've come up with something more devastating.</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">As I speak, our engineers are extracting the resources from Phantasy Star 5,</line>
		<line id="23000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">and merging the data with the game itself and our own brand of file system-corrupting code.</line>
		<line id="24000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">Don't do anything stupid, Mademoiselle.</line>
		<narration>In Real Life, Nozomi whispers to Yuki.<comment>Cut to Yuki and Nozomi sitting on the bed in Yuki's room.</comment></narration>
		<line id="25000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Hey, honey.</line>
		<line id="26000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Let's do something stupid.</line>
		<narration>The Game.</narration>
		<line id="27000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">I heard that.</line>
		<narration>Enemies fill the room and wreck up the place. NoLifeQueen and Satchmo are still pinned to the ground. In Real Life, they whisper.<comment>Stay focused on NoLifeQueen and Satchmo.</comment></narration>
		<line id="28000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Perfect &#x2014; I'll cover you, you go through the escape tunnel at the end of the room.</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<line id="29000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">I'll never leave you behind, my love.</line>
				<line id="30000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Oh, stop &#x2014; you know how your flattery depresses me.</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<line id="31000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Okay!</line>
				<narration>Nozomi laughs.</narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>The two make ready their plan.<comment>Ramp up a sound. Any action from the player sets everything off.</comment></narration>
		<line id="32000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Three  &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="33000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Two  &#x2014;</line>
		<condition>	
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen dashes off.</narration>
				<line id="34000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">Yuki, no!</line>
				<narration>The enemies are surprised! Most charge after Satchmo.</narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen stays.</narration>
				<line id="35000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">One!</line>
				<narration>NoLifeQueen dashes off. The enemies expected something like that. Most charge after NoLifeQueen.</narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<line id="36000" speaker="satchmo_omega" voicelang="ja">Survive! Only the real survive!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen runs to the escape tunnel entrance. She jumps in and then the game environment changes and she's for some reason not in an escape tunnel.</narration>
		<line id="37000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">What &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="38000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">It's taking effect! Already, the input/output corruption errors are occurring.</line>
		<line id="39000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">What the hell!</line>
		<line id="40000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">My Clan is quite large and will take care of you shortly,</line>
		<line id="41000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">but I'm always game for some one-on-one!</line>
		<narration>They get into a fight. As the fight goes on, the environment continues to shift in shape and size and form and location. A shift. The man is gone. NoLifeQueen is in the escape tunnel. She cheers.</narration>
		<line id="42000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Hey, I made it to the escape tunnel.</line>
		<narration>Surrounded by the enemy.<comment>Cut to further away view.</comment></narration>
		<line id="43000" speaker="enemy" voicelang="ja">Get her!</line>
		<narration>They chase NoLifeQueen through the tunnel and over the bridge and through the bridge and through the bridge and over the tunnel and through the bridge and around the cliff then off the cliff then off the cliff again. Everybody falls and falls and falls and then falls again and then finally falls to the ground.<comment>Black out screen.</comment></narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen comes to. Her head is pinned to the railing of the bridge. She opens her eyes. Surrounded. One hundred enemies.<comment>Zoom out here, too.</comment>NoLifeQueen against a world.</narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen loses. Game Over.</narration>
		<narration>Yuki throws her computer at her bed. She thrashes about.<comment>Player can move her around but not prevent her from thrashing. Yuki occasionally pushes the cursor away.</comment><comment>After this point in the game, computers in the Studio break extremely frequently.</comment></narration>
	</part>
</scriptment>