<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="74000" point="segasega" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-10-19" status="final">
	<part>
		<narration>Wednesday morning. 5 o'clock. Yuki silently closes her apartment door, leaving the note that she hoped would say more.<comment>Sudden cut.</comment></narration>
		<narration><comment>If the Player hired Haruka, she does not attend; Sebastian takes her place.</comment>The New Parisian-Nagoyan Network hangs on the bars of a Japanese connector. The lights flicker. The Pommes stare at the signs. The separate groups of passengers yawn. The walls fly by. Yuki looks around. Yuki fidgets. Yuki smirks.</narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Who said we are lost again?</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">In this lonely world?</line>
		<narration>Everyone in the train car looks at Yuki. Everybody in the train car joins in.</narration>
		<line id="3000" speaker="takuya" voicelang="en">I say we can start again?</line>
		<line id="4000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="en">We're on the same ship.</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">It's called starship Earth!</line>
		<narration>The train-lights go off.<comment>Everything but Nozomi blurs.</comment>Nozomi, under the only lit bulb, plays with her hair.</narration>
		<line id="6000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Hello, Nozomi~</line>
		<line id="7000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="en">I wanna hold your hand!</line>
		<line id="8000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">I haven't been the same girl since I saw you coming in &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Let's have a toast to the girl in aisle ten!</line>
		<narration>Nozomi kisses Yuki. All train riders applaud. The hand-holding different-landed gentlemen stare.</narration>
		<line id="10000" speaker="gentlemen" voicelang="en">You're &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="11000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">I don't swing that way, my wife does.</line>
		<narration>All train riders laugh. Yuki raises a hand. All train riders stop.</narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Sonic boom~</line>
		<narration>All train riders scratch their heads. All train riders shrug.</narration>	
		<line id="13000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="en">Sonic boom, sonic boom, sonic boom~</line>
		<line id="14000" speaker="ganpu" voicelang="en">Toot toot sonic warrior!</line>
		<narration>The train riders join in.</narration>
		<line id="15000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Sonic boom, sonic boom, sonic boom~</line>
		<line id="16000" speaker="traingoers" voicelang="en">Toot toot sonic warrior!</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="dan" voicelang="en">Sonic boom, sonic boom, sonic boom~</line>
		<line id="18000" speaker="traingoers" voicelang="en">Toot toot sonic warrior!</line>
		<line id="19000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Sonic boom, sonic boom, sonic boom~</line>
		<narration><comment>Dolly out extremely far from the train through the window as they sing.</comment>Onward travel passengers to the dawn.<comment>Sudden cut.</comment></narration>
		<line id="20000" speaker="lady" voicelang="en">Welcome to Nagoya!</line>
		<narration>The lady cries.</narration>
		<line id="21000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">Headquarters of The Group.</line>
		<narration>From the train exit The Salarymen. The Frenchman breaks his hand from the Japanese man and runs to the meeting area. The Japanese man folds his arms and grimaces. The New Parisian-Nagoyan Network continues down the train platform stairs. Everyone screeches to a halt. A crowd? Yuki stares.</narration>
		<line id="22000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Who are all of you?</line>
		<narration>The Japanese man responds.</narration>
		<line id="23000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">We came to see this "Takeshi" person.</line>
		<narration>The New Parisian-Nagoyan Network scatters, making preparations. Some of them break through creaky floorboards. Some of them trip over shattered stone structures. Some of them step on broken glass. Yuki raises a brow.</narration>
		<line id="24000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Well, she's here.</line>
		<narration>The man looks around. Yuki sighs.</narration>
		<line id="25000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">It's me.</line>
		<line id="26000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">Oh. A Pomme.</line>
		<line id="27000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">That would explain that discontented Frenchman.</line>
		<narration>The Frenchman retorts.</narration>
		<line id="28000" speaker="man" voicelang="fr">That would explain that intolerant Japanese man.</line>
		<line id="29000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">We have a right to be intolerant, this is our land!</line>
		<line id="30000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">You are all but apples falling from the branches of your withering tree,</line>
		<line id="31000" speaker="man" voicelang="ja">to invade our fertile ground&#x2014;</line>
		<narration>The Frenchman punches the Japanese man's face. The Japanese man punches the Frenchman's face. Fists A-fly between Pomme and Nip. Yuki sighs.</narration>
		<narration>Nozomi stands on a platform. The edge crumbles. For balance, she grabs one of the  flagpoles.</narration>
		<line id="33000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">The lighters are ready for you, honey!</line>
		<line id="34000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Fantastic.</line>
		<narration><comment>Player move Yuki to the platform. All blurs but Yuki and her goal.</comment >Yuki passes through the fistfight. She trips over some rocks. Nozomi helps Yuki onto the platform. Yuki looks at the lighters. One BIC. one Sarome. The different-landed so-called "gentlemen" take damages. Faces hit fists hit stomachs hit feet hit low crotches. Yuki turns her back to the violent and faces the wicked.</narration>
		<line id="36000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">The Group is not a game studio, it's a game factory!</line>
		<line id="37000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">You want to know Japan's true Last Video Game Company?</line>
		<narration>A Group employee opens the window. The wind howls. Why is it so easy to open these windows? The employee looks down. The employee snaps out of it. He shoves his head through the window.</narration>
		<line id="38000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">Cave!</line>
		<narration>And another.</narration>
		<line id="39000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">tri-Ace!</line>
		<narration>And another.</narration>
		<line id="40000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">Nintendo!</line>
		<narration>And another.</narration>
		<line id="41000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">TOSE!</line>
		<line id="42000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">What? A blind monkey could hold a higher standard than TOSE.</line>
		<line id="43000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">You take that back!</line>
		<line id="44000" speaker="the_group" voicelang="ja">You stop messing up our ports!</line>
		<narration>The Group employees go on and on about how one guy stepped on the toes of another guy and they shouldn't have sold this or made that or used them or messed with they or&#x2014;</narration>
		<line id="45000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">What a shame.</line>
		<line id="46000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">The Group, a massive blob of separated people!</line>
		<line id="47000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Lost souls, drowning in a sea of their own profit!</line>
		<line id="47100" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">I will show you the power of a connected family of individuals!</line>
		<line id="48000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Behold, the New Parisian-Nagoyan Network's first and only demonstration to The Group!</line>
		<narration>Yuki lights a flag on fire.<comment>The player can move around and light more flags on fire. Every lit flag increases Employee morale.</comment>The violent turn to look at this "Takeshi" person.</narration>
		<line id="49000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Who is Japan's Last Video Game Company?</line>
		<line id="50000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">Sega!</line>
		<line id="51000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Louder, prouder!</line>
		<line id="52000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">Sega!</line>
		<line id="53000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Prouder, louder!</line>
		<line id="54000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">Sega!</line>
		<line id="55000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">To be this good takes Ages!</line>
		<line id="56000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">To be this good takes&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="57000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">Sega!</line>
		<line id="58000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">My name is Yuki Soleil-Takeshi, and I am not Japanese!</line>
		<line id="59000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">My name is Yuki Soleil-Takeshi, and I am not French!</line>
		<line id="60000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">My name is Yuki Soleil-Takeshi, and I am Real!</line>
		<narration>The wind blows through Yuki's hair. Yuki holds her fist in place. Some metal sheets fall down in the distance. Everyone stares at Yuki. The flaming flags continue to flap. The sun rises a little. A person claps. The people clap. Humanity claps! Humanity cheers!</narration>
		<narration>Yuki traverses the platform &#x2014; the stage, caressing the fire. She embraces it. She cherishes it. With each hand, by each hand, she holds one people. Yuki Takeshi Bridges the Gap.<comment>Camera sudden shift to the beat between Yuki's stage and Asami's stage.</comment></narration>
		<narration>The Group bursts through the front doors of their headquarters, taser and club in arm.</narration>
		<line id="61000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Run!</line>
		<narration>Yuki and her comrades run opposite of the train, down the streets of Nagoya, toward Tokyo.<comment>Player is mainly in charge of running.</comment> Through the window of an inconspicuous building breaks a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former designer cheers. Yuki vanishes and dooms the Group member.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former producer cheers. Yuki debug modes the Group member.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former gamer cheers. Yuki parries fifteen kicks.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former designer cheers. Yuki locks the Group member in a windowless, doorless room.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former programmer cheers. Yuki goes into god mode.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former musician cheers. Yuki press turns.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former legend cheers. Yuki stomps a shell.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former engineer cheers. Yuki at once clears four lines.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former writer cheers. Yuki uses a killer move.</narration>
		<narration>From behind an inconspicuous building charges a Group member. From a mass of commuters, a former executive cheers. Yuki hides in the mass. Her comrades hide in the mass.</narration>
		<narration>The Group's members charge past Yuki and company. From a mass of commuters, a former arcade manager cheers. The Network jumps into the conveniently placed corporate-supplied sports cars nearby. All ride into the Tokyo sunrise.<comment>Fade out.</comment></narration>
		<narration>The sun is barely reaching overhead. The New Parisian-Nagoyan Network lay on the ground before headquarters, stretched out. Everyone sighs. Dan rushes back, in hand a camera.</narration>
		<line id="62000" speaker="dan" voicelang="ja">Guys, this is the perfect time to make our new intro video!</line>
		<line id="63000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">Intro video?</line>
		<line id="64000" speaker="dan" voicelang="ja">Yeah, like one that shows our logo.</line>
		<line id="65000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">You mean, an intro video that actually has people in it?</line>
		<line id="66000" speaker="dan" voicelang="ja">Recording.</line>
		<narration>Dan presses the record hands Yuki the camera. Yuki points the camera at the employees.<comment>First person shooting. The player controls the camera. If the player points the camera at someone who didn't have anything planned for the video at the time, they point at someone else. Where the camera points controls the behaviors of the people it's pointed toward.</comment></narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<comment>The player points the camera at Shimizu.</comment>
				<narration>Shimizu hides behind Takuya.</narration>
				<line id="67000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">No, I'm a criminal, don't take pictures of me.</line>
				<narration>Takuya waves at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="67100" speaker="takuya" voicelang="en">Hello!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<comment>The Player points the camera at Dan.</comment>
				<narration>Dan pounds fists with Ganpu. The two laugh. They wave at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="68000" speaker="dan" voicelang="en">We've got balls of steel.</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="3">
				<comment>The Player points the camera at Lori.</comment>
				<narration>Lori winks at Takuya. She looks back at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="69000" speaker="lori" voicelang="fr">I will not work for any other corporation or with any other people.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<comment>The Player points the camera at Nozomi.</comment>
				<narration>Nozomi gets in the way of the camera and hugs Yuki. She pulls back and waves at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="70000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Hello!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<comment>The Player points the camera at Ganpu.</comment>
				<narration>Ganpu looks at Yuki and sighs and smiles.</narration>
				<line id="71000" speaker="ganpu" voicelang="en">What's up, America?</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="3">
				<comment>The Player points the camera at Hanako again.</comment>
				<narration>Hanako shields her face with her jacket.</narration>
				<line id="72000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">I shouldn't have done this. I did something shameful.</line>
				<narration>Takuya pats her on the back.</narration>
				<line id="73000" speaker="takuya" voicelang="ja">Come on now, you're ruining the party!</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<comment>The Player turns the camera to Nozomi.</comment>
				<narration>Nozomi waves at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="74000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="en">We are all the Omega!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<comment>The Player turns the camera to Ganpu.</comment>
				<narration>Ganpu winks at the camera.</narration>
				<line id="75000" speaker="ganpu" voicelang="en">We are all the most fitting introduction to our finale.</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="3">
				<comment>The Player turns the camera to Takuya.</comment>
				<narration>Takuya fist-pumps.</narration>
				<line id="76000" speaker="takuya" voicelang="en">We are all the final chapter of the world's greatest legend.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>Yuki turns the camera to herself.</narration>
		<line id="77000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">We are all Sega.</line>
		<narration>Yuki places herself with the whole team.</narration>
		<line id="78000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">And we are all the New Parisian-Nagoyan Network!</line>
		<line id="79000" speaker="team" voicelang="ja">Yeah! Go New PNN! We are all the best&#x2014;</line>
		<narration>Hanako picks up the camera .<comment>Stay in first person perspective.</comment>Shimizu slams the camera.</narration>
		<line id="80000" speaker="takuya" voicelang="ja">Hey, what's the deal&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="81000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">I can't condone this!</line>
		<line id="82000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">I just helped you all demolish private property!</line>
		<line id="83000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">And for what?</line>
		<narration>Hanako points at Yuki.</narration>
		<line id="84000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">This suspicious blonde's own self-fulfillment!</line>
		<line id="85000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Calm down, Shimizu&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="86000" speaker="hanako" voicelang="ja">Hanako! My name is Hanako!</line>
		<narration>Hanako leaves.</narration>
	</part>
</scriptment>