<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="81000" point="group_headquarters" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-10-30" status="final">
	<part>
		<line id="1000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Madame Soleil, I believe you are familiar with the exterior of our facilities.</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">I heard some rowdy twenty-something came along and singed the banners.</line>
		<line id="3000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Surely no issue if flags represent not your passions.</line>
		<narration>The Demomen glare at Soleil. Soleil clutches Nozomi's hand. The Demomen continue.</narration>
		<line id="3100" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Welcome to the present, the future, the Pride and Glory of the Japanese game industry.</line>
		<line id="4000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Enjoy the tour of our wonderful facilities.</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Remember:</line>
		<line id="6000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Your response. Immediately.</line>
		<narration>All enter the building.</narration>
		<narration>Transparent light emitting diode monitors are all neatly tiled amongst the space's walls. Same-landed employes in straight-pressed suits light-march across the harshly shining stark-white floors. Abysses of stories of servers whir in purposeless orchestration.</narration>
		<line id="21000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">We have a single, unified facility where all studios and equipment are one.</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Next, let us view the outsourcing facility.</line>
		<narration>The Demomen, Soleil, and Nozomi enter a glass elevator. The elevator rises to the center area of the facility. Before the tour-guides and tour-takers &#x2014; people on fours creep cross the floor. Those on break are too tired to eat. Those on work are too weary to type. Those clocking out are ready to weep.</narration>
		<line id="23000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">They're &#x2014; so young &#x2014; these &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="24000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">These are interns!</line>
		<narration>The Demomen laugh. Computational smokes tarnish the already-thin air. A Draft comes in and loudly blows the smog and tar about. One Demoman puts his sole to an intern's struggling brow. </narration>
		<line id="25000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">Survival of the fittest.</line>
		<line id="26000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">At The Group, all workers earn their positions.</line>
		<narration>The Demomen glare at Soleil. Soleil scoffs. The Demomen continue.</narration>
		<line id="27000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">And if they don't make it, what to them do you do?</line>
		<line id="28000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">It's not what we do. It's what they do.</line>
		<narration>A computer monitor flies past Soleil's face. The monitor slams against a desk. Soleil gasps. An intern begins his Dash.<comment>Slow motion. Soleil looks at the Player and points at the Dasher. The Player can direct Soleil to chase him. Soleil runs as far as the Player will take her. Realize: He is faster than She.</comment></narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>Soleil rushes at the Dasher, grabs at the Dasher, reaches for the Dasher. <comment>Zoom out.</comment>Bare and naked at the end of the line is a hole where used to be a window. The Dasher leaps. At the balcony Soleil thumps. Hand loose and tense and all a-thrust, she screams over the edge.</narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>Soleil hesitates. In mid-stride she slips and then drops. Every stomp of the Dasher's run ripples the ground.<comment>Zoom out slowly to keep Dasher in view at all times.</comment>Bare and naked at the end of the line is a hole where used to be a window. The Dasher leaps. At the floor Soleil thumps. Hand loose and tense and all a-thrust, she screams across the ground.</narration>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>Soleil weeps and wails and The Demomen drag her by the feet back towards that oh-so-beautiful elevator as the clumps about her lashes remain unaffected by her tears and Nozomi kneels down next to her and holds her tight. Soleil yells:</narration>
		<line id="29000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">Stop hiring interns!</line>
		<line id="30000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">They can't handle the load! You can't keep them here!</line>
		<line id="31000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">If interns cannot hold their lunch, you cannot hold your breath.</line>
		<narration>Soleil puffs.</narration>
		<line id="32000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">Next, we will visit our History Center.</line>
		<line id="33000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">History Center?</line>
		<line id="34000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">Yes, for without record of our legacy, we have nothing.</line>
		<line id="35000" speaker="nozomi" voicelang="ja">Decades of stagnation, a "legacy."</line>
		<line id="36000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">More of a legacy than your "Sonic Adventure Portable," eh Hasegawa?</line>
		<narration>Nozomi folds her arms. The elevator reaches its destination. All exit.<comment>Zoom out.</comment> More transparent monitors. Now, they litter not only the walls but the walkways and the air and the floor.</narration>
		<line id="37000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">Behold; this is home to four decades of digitized commit logs.</line>
		<narration>A Demoman presses the button. The screens all change to a font monospaced. Their interpretation of the History of Video Games is shown. Soleil observes the ones she can read:</narration>
		<line id="38000" speaker="game">1983. gave jump-man a friend. -- s. miyamoto</line>
		<line id="39000" speaker="game">1985. put princess far away. -- t. tezuka</line>
		<line id="40000" speaker="game">1986. made kunio move up and down too. -- y. kishimoto</line>
		<line id="41000" speaker="game">1986. made battles random -- y. horii</line>
		<line id="42000" speaker="game">1987. screw those guys, our random battles are better!!! -- h. sakaguchi</line>
		<line id="43000" speaker="game">1995. changed warrior hair color to blonde. video cutscenes hard to change. hope u dont mind. -- t. nomura</line>
		<line id="40000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">This is remarkable.</line>
		<narration>The Demomen jump up and down.</narration>
		<line id="41000" speaker="demomen" voicelang="fr">We also have video documentation of internal and external developer activity.</line>
		<narration>A Demoman presses the button. The screens all change to video players. Spontaneous camerawork is shown.<comment>The screen the Player moves Soleil closest to is the one that will be heard.</comment></narration>
		
		
		<condition>
			<narration>Soleil stands at the screen labeled "group_init:"</narration>
			<narration>A sales representative, newspaper in hand, slams the table.</narration>
			<line id="41100" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Parisian-Nagoyan Network's "Flashback Fourth Dimension &#x2014;"</line>
			<line id="41200" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Receives Famitsu Magazine's fourth Perfect Score!</line>
			<line id="41210" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">They didn't even pay them off!</line>
			<line id="41300" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Parisian-Nagoyan Network's "Flashback Fourth Dimension &#x2014;"</line>
			<line id="41400" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Outsells Wind Waker!</line>
			<line id="41410" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">They don't even have Zelda's legacy!</line>
			<narration>A market analyst rubs his chin.</narration>
			<line id="41500" speaker="analyst" voicelang="ja">Well, they've essentially become a more powerful corporate force than we.</line>
			<line id="41600" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">More powerful? We're Nintendo!</line>
			<line id="41700" speaker="analyst" voicelang="ja">Yes, but The PNN is Panasonic and Fujitsu and Canon and Delphine and Adeline and Clickteam&#x2014;</line>
			<line id="41800" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">That's it!</line>
			<line id="41900" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">The PNN is a network of individuals.</line>
			<line id="41910" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">So to beat them, we must become a single powerful force: a Group.</line>
		</condition>
		
		
		
		<condition>	
			<narration>Soleil stands at the screen labeled "old_pnn_sortie:"</narration>
			<narration>The people on screen, all different-landed, flip out their cellphones.</narration>
			<line id="42000" speaker="cuisset" voicelang="fr">This land has some strange mobile phones.</line>
			<narration>The designer operating the camera laughs.</narration>
			<line id="43000" speaker="designer" voicelang="fr">Still though, I bet they're pretty good for gaming.</line>
			<line id="44000" speaker="cuisset" voicelang="fr">At this point, a mobile phone game is all that's in the budget.</line>
			<line id="45000" speaker="designer" voicelang="fr">The damn Group's got us at the finale at the start of the play.</line>
			<line id="46000" speaker="designer" voicelang="fr">After this game is where we must take our Leave.</line>
			<line id="47000" speaker="cuisset" voicelang="fr">Hey, that's a good idea for a name:</line>
			<line id="48000" speaker="cuisset" voicelang="fr">La Sortie.</line>
			<line id="49000" speaker="cuisset" voicelang="fr">La Sortie des Usines Jeux à Lyon.</line>
		</condition>

		<condition>
			<narration>Soleil stands at the screen labeled "group_plan:"</narration>
			<narration>A sales representative, newspaper in hand, slams the table.</narration>
			<line id="50000" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Parisian-Nagoyan Network's "La Sortie&#x2014;"</line>
			<line id="51000" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Receives Famitsu Magazine's eighth Perfect Score!</line>
			<line id="52000" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Parisian-Nagoyan Network's "La Sortie&#x2014;</line>
			<line id="53000" speaker="seller" voicelang="ja">Outsells Metal Gear Solid 4!</line>
			<narration>The sales representative sighs. The analyst smirks.</narration>
			<line id="54000" speaker="analyst" voicelang="ja">Gentlemen.</line>
			<line id="55000" speaker="analyst" voicelang="ja">Let's gun 'em down.</line>
		</condition>
		<narration>All the screens go blank.</narration>
		<line id="56000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Good stuff, huh?</line>
		<line id="57000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Let's move on to The Group's greatest creation.</line>
		<narration>The Demomen rush back into the elevator. Soleil and Nozomi walk back in.</narration>
		<narration>The Demomen press a button. The elevator flies. Hundreds of lights fly by. Through the tight, tight glass permeate the sounds of construction. Through the greenhouse magnifies the sun. The elevator halts. Soleil stumbles. The Demomen stay arms a-fold.</narration>
		<line id="58000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Behold.</line>
		<narration>The elevator opens.<comment>Zoom out extremely far.</comment></narration>
		<narration>Before all is a hulking, steaming, buzzing, fizzling machine. The wires sprawl across the entirety of the roof, half extending back to the abyss of mounted servers below. Fans make to dance the un-natural heat waves. Status lights out-brighten the sun. This is no place for humanity.</narration>
		<line id="59000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">All you see before you,</line>
		<line id="60000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Concept art, Narrative fragments, Musical compositions,</line>
		<line id="61000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Design documents, Source code, Manuals, Advertisement,</line>
		<line id="62000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Interviews, Emails, Full Motion Video Cutscenes &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="63000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Is computer generated.</line>
		<narration>Soleil quivers. The Demomen continue.</narration>
		<line id="64000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Madame Soleil, what you see before you is the greatest invention in the history of video games.</line>
		<line id="65000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">The Brain of Gotanda, the Guitar of Meguro, the Life of Miyamoto,</line>
		<line id="66000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">All condensed into a single machine.</line>
		<line id="67000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">A machine with hundreds of terabytes of random access memory.</line>
		<line id="68000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">A machine with the graphical capability of twenty Pixars.</line>
		<line id="69000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">A machine that, independent of The Group's control, will procedurally generate a blockbuster.</line>
		<line id="70000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="fr">Behold:</line>
		<line id="71000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">RPG Maker 2012.</line>
		<narration>By the collar Soleil grabs a Demoman.</narration>
		<line id="70000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">This is wrong, this is wrong!</line>
		<line id="71000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Video games are made by People!</line>
		<line id="72000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">We are people.</line>
		<line id="73000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">You're a Corporation!</line>
		<line id="74000" speaker="demoman" voicelang="ja">Will you become one with this Corporation?</line>
		<narration>Madame Soleil drops the man to the ground. She trudges to a nearby server rack. She slumps upon it. <comment>Zoom out slowly regardless of interaction. Player can move Soleil at any time.</comment>Nozomi stares at her. The Demoman dance and holler. The surveillance cameras zoom in and out on Soleil. The server fans blow Soleil's hair. She stares over the building's edge. Soleil smiles and laughs the dissonant whirs away:</narration>
		<narration>A Judge bangs his gavel.</narration>
		<line id="75000" speaker="judge" voicelang="ja">I hereby declare the defendant, Mademoiselle Yuki Soleil-Takeshi &#x2014;</line>
		<line id="76000" speaker="judge" voicelang="ja">Innocent!</line>
		<narration>Two Policemen knock their glasses against Soleil's.</narration>
		<line id="77000" speaker="policeman" voicelang="ja">A vodka lover, huh! And more sober than we after a few.</line>
		<narration>He holds his keys out.</narration>
		<line id="78000" speaker="policeman" voicelang="ja">Can you drive us home?</line>
		<narration>The Prime Minister shakes hands with Soleil.</narration>
		<line id="79000" speaker="minister" voicelang="ja">How does it feel, being this land's first legally recognized same-sex spouse &#x2014; Madame?</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen kisses Soleil on the cheek!</narration>
		<line id="80000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Yeah, Madame! How does it feel to be a goddamned sellout?</line>
		<line id="81000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">How do you like retreating to the fake when you need to deal with the real?</line>
		<line id="82000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">How do you like not being alive?</line>
		<narration>The Group! Headquarters! Roof! RPG Maker 2012! Offer! Legal Action! Response &#x2014; &#x2014; &#x2014;</narration>
		<line id="83000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">No!</line>
		<line id="84000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="ja">No!</line>
		<line id="85000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="en">No!</line>
		<narration>Soleil laughs.<comment>She urges the Player to the elevator. It's time to leave.</comment></narration>
		<narration>The Demomen stop dancing.</narration>
		<narration>Nozomi clasps her hands together and grins.</narration>
		<narration>Soleil and Nozomi enter the elevator. Soleil and Nozomi descend to the first floor. Soleil and Nozomi exit the building.</narration>
	</part>
</scriptment>