<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="99000" point="clan9_lyon" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-12-11" status="final">
	<part>
		<narration>Yuki's — NoLifeQueen's — hair blows in the coastline's breeze — nay — hex? UTF-8? Berkeley Sockets?<comment>Zoom out.</comment>Subtle disintegrations permeate the World. It begins to fray.<comment>Begin to disintegrate world from a side, leading Player to have NoLifeQueen run.</comment></narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen makes it into a building. Darkness.<comment>Player fumbles around for a time.</comment></narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">When we get out of this, Yuki, you're gonna get such an apology!</line>
		<line id="2000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="fr">Even I'm excited. After all, this is the end of the line.</line>
		<narration>A crack. In the ceiling. Light. Visibility. The crack becomes a crow. More cracks. More crows. A murder of cracks. A gaggle of crows. Crows swarm around NoLifeQueen. They attack.<comment>Player fights the crows.</comment></narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen's life counter runs to Zero. The avatar splits, into hex. Into UTF-8. Into Berkeley Sockets. Into four NoLifeQueens.<comment>All in the Clan.</comment>NoLifeQueen attacks.</narration>
		<narration>The hundreds of crows morph into snarling biting dark-blue hedgehogs. They rush NoLifeQueen.</narration>
		<narration>The miniature hedgehogs band together and congeal into that enormous blue, spiked, attitude-d abomination. It only has one animation. It slams its fist to the ground. It slams its fist to the ground. It slams its fist to the ground. As if in a video game.</narration>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen wins.</narration>
		<narration>The world around NoLifeQueen begins to shift, morph, transform and convert and restructure and evolve, into something familiar. From the computer's speakers comes:</narration>
		<line id="3000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">If you are reading this,</line>
		<narration>World-renowned recording artist Asami Takeshi's number one song plays.</narration>
		<line id="4000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">You have managed to, through indescribably concocted circumstance,</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">single-handedly crack the encryption of tens of gigabytes of hidden game data.</line>
		<narration>The world shifts and shifts into — into — Lyon! France! Home! NoLifeQueen stands before Home.</narration>
		<line id="6000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">From one to one for every single month, I slaved away at this unstable code.</line>
		<line id="7000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">I tended every line with all my might.</line>
		<line id="8000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">All for my dear, dear, taken-for-granted daughter.</line>
		<line id="9000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">I repurposed the work of a thousand men to tell you, Yuki:</line>
		<line id="10000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">I am sorry.</line>
		<narration><comment>No progression until NoLifeQueen makes it into the home.</comment>NoLifeQueen reaches the commons room.</narration>
		<line id="11000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">Sorry for everything.</line>
		<narration><comment>Blur all parts of the world except the stairs.</comment>NoLifeQueen stops and looks up the stairs. <comment>The camera continues to move upstairs, and Jacques begins to talk to himself in the mirror in the distance.</comment></narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">I want you to know just one thing, Yuki.</line>
		<line id="13000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">Just one thing:</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen is in Yuki's room. She gazes longingly upon Yuki's bed. She soaks up Yuki's sun. She breathes in Yuki's air. All is well.<comment>Blur all but the bed. No progression until the Player guides NoLifeQueen to the bed.</comment>She bathes in Yuki's cradle. Jacques continues.</narration>
		<line id="14000" speaker="jacques" voicelang="fr">Though we all are long gone from home, we all must take home with us.</line>
		<narration>2011. In the soft, luminescent glow of rosy bedsheets reflecting the Lyon morning sun lies NoLifeQueen.</narration>
		<narration>The Clan's impressive credits roll. The hundreds of so-well-involved team members and organizations and software libraries' names flow gracefully upward to the edge of the screen — which gets chucked into the garbage can.</narration>
		<narration>Yuki gets up. Yuki pushes her chair in. Yuki's face is blank.<comment>Yuki urges the Player extremely close to her face. She stares at the camera.</comment></narration>
		<line id="15000" speaker="yuki" voicelang="fr">Video games are dead.</line>
		<narration><comment>Yuki wrestles away the Player's control.</comment>Yuki throws over her shelf of so-called classics. Yuki kicks over her boxes and cubes and casts. Yuki fist-cracks some liquid crystal displays.<comment>Yuki begins to take interface elements and toss them away. She breaks the money display, kicks the action buttons, glares at the Player's cursor.</comment>She stands in place.<comment>When the Player attempts to move Yuki, Yuki grabs the path the player draws and crumples it up.</comment><comment>Sudden cut fast between all of these actions:</comment>Yuki gets her coats and dresses and make-up cases. She stuffs into them as many video game boxes as possible. She wraps them all in a bedsheet. She ties the bedsheet to a string. She gets her lighter fluid. She gets her lighter.</narration>
		<narration>Yuki leaves her house and begins to march toward Headquarters, dragging with her the bed-sheet of past-times.<comment>The Player no longer controls Yuki. The Player's interactions are god-like now, manipulating the world and people around Yuki to inhibit her march.</comment>Nozomi lingers but a stumble away, grabbing at Yuki, being dragged by Yuki, begging Yuki to stop. Yuki pays all attention to memory:</narration>
		<line id="16000" speaker="news" voicelang="fr">— Ubisoft files for bankruptcy. Employees often blame the Software Identity Act —</line>
		<line id="17000" speaker="news" voicelang="ja">— The Group's RPG Maker 2012 becomes too costly a development prospect —</line>
		<line id="18000" speaker="news" voicelang="ja">— 95% of professional game development studios unable to find publishers —</line>
		<line id="19000" speaker="news" voicelang="en">— EA Games' entire christmas lineup has been canceled —</line>
		<line id="20000" speaker="news" voicelang="en">— Consumer interest in video games drops 50,000% —</line>
		<line id="21000" speaker="news" voicelang="fr">— Social demographic for video games diminishes to Males 2-7; —</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="news" voicelang="en">— The Group Nintendo Branch buries remaining Nintendo DS cartridges in a landfill —</line>
		<narration>Headquarters. In the heat of the server room, Yuki out-spreads the bedsheet. She pushes Nozomi away. She pours onto bush and shrub and bedsheet the lighter fluid. She drops upon the concoction her flame. Yuki caresses her own cheek. She stares down upon the fire. She embraces it. She cherishes it.</narration>
		<narration>Headquarters roof. The escalate wind blows Yuki's fringe to the sky. Smoke fills this upper air. Yuki stands at structure's edge. She looks to the heavens. She smiles. She looks to the rising smoke. The lady breathes hard. She shuts her lids, spreads her arms, and forward drifts.</narration>
	</part>
</scriptment>