<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Project Yuki Original English Scriptment
Copyright (C) 2010 Kyle Reynolds

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.-->



<?xml-stylesheet href="yuki.css" type="text/css"?>
<scriptment id="48000" point="clan5_rooftops" localizationstatus="original" fictionaldate="2011-08-11" status="final">
	<part>
		<narration><comment>Cut to church bell, ding four times leading into Get On It. After the fourth ding, start piano riff. NoLifeQueen appears on screen.</comment>NoLifeQueen flies past the church bell, through her dress the wind a-blowing.<comment>Impressment opportunity. Player hits the ground running. Camera does not follow NoLifeQueen on the way down. Cut to running.</comment></narration>
		<line id="1000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Yeah!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen hits the ground running, Clan in tow. Something is amiss &#x2014; everyone's account passwords are showing directly under their usernames.<comment>Bass riff. Game controls camera for a bit.</comment>NoLifeQueen, Davis, and their Clans clamor down the cobbled street.<comment>And right at the beginning of the chorus, dolly out.</comment>Everyone's excited! This is going to be a great time!<comment>And then at the end of the bridge&#x2014;</comment>In rushes a bursting blast of blinding steam.</narration>
		<line id="2000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Everyone on the roof!</line>
		<narration>Not much better. Player names become garbled. Passwords disappear. Items become invisible. All is obscured from view but friend, foe, and ground. The steam rages on.<comment>Have the steam not be there for a few seconds when the player reaches the roof. Items should be present in the area, to show that they are not visible when the steam is around.</comment></narration>
		<line id="3000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">What was that?</line>
		<line id="4000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Encryption system!</line>
		<line id="5000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">It protects user accounts &#x2014; it's actually better to keep the steam here.</line>
		<line id="6000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">We've got to keep the steam going!</line>
		<narration>The steam sporadically disappears, leaving sensitive information out in the open. IP Addresses, SSH public keys, passwords, email addresses &#x2014; a wrench falls from the sky.</narration>
		<line id="7000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Get that wrench and fix the valves!</line>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen reaches for the wrench and an opponent grabs it and runs off. NoLifeQueen chases him!<comment>This portion of the level is straightforward: the more fixed valves, the more users. To fix a valve, the player has to go up to one with the wrench and Fix as Main Action. This takes a while. To prevent the player from backtracking, the steam gets incredibly thick and deals damage the further back she goes.</comment></narration>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>Davis gets the wrench and fixes a valve. NoLifeQueen protects him.</narration>
				<line id="7100" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Magical Girl, I need a shield!</line>
				<line id="8000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">I'll keep you covered!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen gets the wrench and fixes a valve. Davis protects her.</narration>
				<line id="8100" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Hold on Dave, I'm turning a wrench.</line>
				<line id="9000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">I've got your back.</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>Everyone makes their way across the rooftops, grabbing wrenches and fixing valves. After a point, the steam becomes so thick that all is obscured.</narration>
		<line id="10000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Success!</line>
		<narration>The steam subsides. The two are alone, no longer amongst the area of encryption.</narration>
		<line id="11000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Where are we?</line>
		<narration>Davis gasps. He grabs NoLifeQueen.<comment>Ramp up the music here.</comment></narration>
		<line id="12000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">You're grabbing me! Someone's cracking your computer!</line>
		<line id="12100" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">No, nobody—</line> 
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen breaks free of Davis' grip. She stands, bewildered. Davis is shocked.</narration>
				<line id="13000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Yuki, why&#x2014;</line>
				<narration>Train hits them both.<comment>Both lose health, but they remain together. Davis stays in the party.</comment></narration>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen stays in Davis' grip. He throws her into the air. Davis breathes a sigh of relief and train hits him.<comment>Only Davis gets hit, only Davis loses health. The two are now separated. NoLifeQueen is alone.</comment></narration>
				<line id="14000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Dave, no! Bro!</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>NoLifeQueen ends up on the roof of the train. She takes a look around. <comment>Dolly out extremely far from the train.</comment>This train looks like...</narration>
		<line id="15000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">This is &#x2014; a loading screen?</line>
		<line id="14100" speaker="game">Telechargement...</line>
		<condition>
			<choice number="1">
				<narration><comment>Davis and NoLifeQueen are together.</comment>Davis looks ahead.</narration>
				<line id="16000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">There are a lot of users loading the game right now.</line>
				<line id="17000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">There's malware up ahead &#x2014; at 100% loaded, the users are all screwed.</line>
				<comment>A percentage loaded bar appears at the top of the screen. Camera get a look at this bomb.</comment>
				<line id="18000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">We've gotta stop the train!</line>
			</choice>
			<choice number="2">
				<narration>NoLifeQueen is alone, resting on the top of the train.</narration>
				<line id="19000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">What is that?</line>
				<comment>Camera get a look at this bomb.</comment>
				<line id="20000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">That's a bomb! I've got to stop it!</line>
			</choice>
		</condition>
		<narration>Davis comes over the microphone-chat.</narration>
		<line id="20100" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">These are all newbies!</line>
		<line id="21000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">We can't let these end-users' first experience with The Clan be a crash!</line>
		<line id="22000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Let's try to get into the train.</line>

		<narration><comment>Player follow Davis to the interior of the train.</comment>Davis and NoLifeQueen bust into the train. Every passenger turns and points a gun.</narration>
		<line id="23000" speaker="passenger" voicelang="ja">What are you doing here?</line>
		<line id="24000" speaker="davis" voicelang="ja">Nobody move! We're trying to&#x2014;</line>
		<line id="25000" speaker="passenger" voicelang="en">This must be the first battle! Get those guys!</line>
		<narration>Everyone charges after Davis and NoLifeQueen. Davis echoes over the microphone.</narration>
		<line id="26000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Don't defeat them &#x2014; these are potential players.</line>
		<line id="27000" speaker="nolifequeen" voicelang="en">Get to the missile launcher and destroy that bomb!</line>
		<narration>Game's afoot.<comment>Train is very fast. Nobody fall off or else dead. The player must enter the train and launch missiles at the bomb in the distance.</comment><comment>After destroying the bomb, NoLifeQueen and Davis take a breather.</comment></narration>
		<line id="28000" speaker="davis" voicelang="en">Phew.</line>2
		<narration>Davis and NoLifeQueen stand tall and then the passengers bust into their cab.</narration>
		<line id="29000" speaker="passenger" voicelang="lt">There they are!</line>
		<narration>The entire population of passengers defeats NoLifeQueen and Davis. Game Over.</narration>
	</part>
</scriptment>